Fear starts at midnight
Minutes Past Midnight is a horror, thriller film directed by James Moran.
As midnight falls, all manner of terror invades the Earth.
Demons, cannibals, killers, ghosts and monsters swarm the world in these tales
of the supernatural, the fantastic, and the just plain horrific.
Featuring nine stories of horror.
Nicholas Grimshaw (segment 'The Mill At Calder's End'), played by Jason Flemyng.
The Apparition of the Mill (segment 'The Mill At
Calder's End'), played by Barbara Steele.
Harrison Grimshaw (segment 'The Mill At Calder's End'), played by Piotr Michael.
Caylie (segment 'Awake'), played by Mika Boorem.
Charlie (segment: Crazy For You), played by Arthur Darvill.
Michael (segment 'Ghost Train'), played by Owen McDonnell.
The Doomsday Clock is a symbol that represents the estimated likelihood of a human-made global
catastrophe, in the opinion of the nonprofit organization Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists.
Maintained since 1947, the Clock is a proxy mechanism for threats to humanity from unchecked scientific and technological advances: A hypothetical global catastrophe is
represented by midnight on the Clock, with the Bulletin's opinion on how close the world is to "zero"  represented by a certain number of minutes or seconds to midnight.
This is assessed in January of each year.
The main factors influencing the Clock are nuclear warfare,
climate change, and artificial intelligence.
The Bulletin's Science and Security Board monitors new developments in the life
sciences and technology that could inflict irrevocable harm to humanity.
The Clock's original setting in 1947 was seven minutes to midnight.
It has since been set backward eight times and forward 18 times.
The farthest time from midnight was 17 minutes in 1991, and
the closest is 89 seconds, set in January 2025.
The Clock was moved to 150 seconds (2 minutes, 30 seconds) in 2017, then forward
to two minutes to midnight in 2018, and left unchanged in 2019.
It was moved forward to 100 seconds (1 minute, 40 seconds) in 2020, 90 seconds (1
minute, 30 seconds) in 2023, and 89 seconds (1 minute, 29 seconds) in 2025.
The film explores themes of monster, haunting, gore, anthology, creature.
The tone is dark and intense.